(Amy:)That'd be my boyfriend...
...happier playing his Star Trek game
with friends than hanging out with me.
(Raj:)- Wars.
- What?
(Penny:)Star Wars. They get all cranky
when you mix the two up.
- What's the difference?
- There's absolutely no difference.
(Amy:)How do I get him to treat me better?
(Penny:)All right, let me give you
a little GirIfriend 101.
Usually the first move is you withhold sex...
(Penny:)...but that will work better
after Sheldon hits puberty.
So l'd say give him the silent treatment.
- No, he loves that.
- Hmm.
(Amy:)Our record for sitting in a room together
and not speaking...
...is six and a haIf hours.
He said it was a magical evening.
All right, we're gonna have
to go with an oldie but goodie:
(Penny:)- Making a scene.
- l don't think l'd be good at that.
Ah. You're lucky to have me.
Back in Omaha...
...there are two restaurants
I'm not allowed into. Both Chili's.